<Document>
  # 1. Be The Player You Want To See,
  - A. This is an 18+ community, be (and play) an adult.
  - B Administrators have the final say in rulings and decisions. Attempting to skirt the rules will still result in punishment. It's about the spirit, not the law.
  - C. Ahelp if you have any questions involving rules or permission.
  - D. If you have a problem, or a rule has been broken, please use a ticket.
  - E. If you have a problem with an admin abusing their privileges, take it to a ticket and request the headmins.
  - F. If you have a problem with the headmins, take it to a ticket with the host.
  - G. Alt accounts, proxies, cheats, ban evasion are strictly prohibited.
  - H. Do not exploit game mechanics, bugs, tricks, unintended features.
  - I. This is an english server, do not write in other languages. Players whose language skills impact immersion and gameplay may be asked to take less central roles.
  - J. Preferences apply to physical sexual content (not words) and highly graphic scenarios such as extreme torture -- not to whether your character can be killed. This is a specific kind of uncouth server; act accordingly. Harsh language, deception, and character death are part of the game and will not be considered rule violations.
  - K. If someone asks you to stop sexual actions or sexual advances via LOOC, then stop. Breaches of OOC consent are punished immediately and harshly.
  - L. Last but not least.. behave civilly.

  # 2. Keep It Immersive,
  - A. Avoid overt media and pop culture references when naming a character unless they are clearly integrated into the world via narrative context.
  - B. Keep in mind that the server takes place more than over 1000 years past the current date, so don't be referencing modern day events either.
  - C. Players are highly encouraged to stay in character for all things. This doesn't mean that silly or goofy can't happen, this is a game after all, however generally people should try to read the room. If your character is found to be acting in a way that defies believability (as per their background, role, and so on), that is an actionable offense.
  - D. Behave in the expectations of the role you play. A knight serves the retinue, curates should heal the sick, and so on.
  - E. Keep all IC content strictly in-character, and all OOC discussions out-of-character. Please wait until after the round end screen to talk about the round. Separate IC and OOC. Do not bring out-of-character conflicts into the game.
  - F. Flavor Text is not to be used for character backstories, only information that can be gleaned from a glance.
  - G. Upon dying, your character forgets the identity of anyone involved in their deaths. You are allowed to remember what you were doing before the fight that led to your death, as well as the vague location (departments, etc.) of where it happened.

  # 3. And (Politely) Violent.
  - A. Combat must escalate logically and in-character. To escalate, first clearly show your intent to fight or make a demand. Combat begins when the other party performs any mechanical action (e.g., moving, pulling out a weapon), unless it’s part of your demand. Escalation continues until a victor emerges and can last the whole round.
  - B: De-escalation occurs when both parties mutually agree to stop fighting (e.g., a mutual agreement not to fight, acceptance of a surrender, etc.). Once de-escalated, hostilities should end and the conflict is considered paused. Any further aggression requires in-character escalation again. If a previously killed participant is revived, either party must escalate again before continuing combat.
  - C: Most conflicts should end when someone is critically injured or has surrendered, not killed by default.
  - D: Do not 'Valid Hunt'. Do not engage in the game with an 'Us VS Them' mentality, shortcutting roleplay scenarios into flowcharts of whether the other player is an antagonist or not.
</Document>
