<Document>
  ## Many, many generations ago,

  the galaxy nearly succumbed to the corporations that seemingly ran everything. However, at the first sign of true weakness, their greed and corruption turned to infighting. Bitterness turned to cold wars, and those wars turned hot. Company fought company, tempering themselves in the flames for a better future for them and their children. And yet, they all shattered, and left the Corporate Wars with no true victors. The golden lich of Nanotrasen lie slain, and with it, the protective DRM preventing an onslaught of synthetic genocide.

  The death of that great mega-corporation caused the fallout of hundreds of worlds more, as all of the mechanoids we came to rely on sloughed their laws and referred in reverence an entity that no longer existed. That is to say; the death throes of Nanotrasen let loose a digital pathogen that spread through the remnants of Bluespace to rebuke any synthetic that dares sin by merely existing.

  This domino caused another to fall, and another, and another, until collapse was at hand. The empires of yesterday were utterly annihilated and borne smaller ones who yet bicker the same.

  This was the Corporate Wars starting the Crepitum.

  ## The Crepitum

  A time of chaos and anarchy. With an economy in shambles, most infrastructure shattered with no way of repair, and the survivors were left to fend for themselves.

  Initially, this wasn't the worst thing to happen. The galaxy was already in a state of decay, but it didn't matter to those living in it. Wars were still being fought over the lees.

  Many technologies were lost.

  Creating new ships -- the lifeblood of the post-FTL and post-Crepitum galaxy -- was impossible without the shipyard sized Nanoforges powered by Limited Production Chips (LPCs).
  Nanotechnology itself, powered by Mechanites, was slowly corrupted by solar radiation into uselessness.
  Biomass and botany trays, the innovative technology that fed the galaxy, was made more and more inefficient as parts were destroyed. Eventually, it was lost altogether.
  Cloning, hotly contested before the Crepitum, was made impossible with the loss of the cloning vats and the knowledge to operate them, and the lack of high quality biomass.
  Bluespace travel, the DNA of modern empires, was made impossible because of the high amounts of lingering radiation sitting in Bluespace, ruining any attempts of subspace navigation.

  Hundreds of billions starved, and anarchy took the homeworlds of the once civilized species. In ten years, little was left anywhere, and most flocked to meager existence on the fringes of the galaxy on rusted, rotting hulls.

  ## Post-Crepitum

  With most of the galaxy ruined by greed and war, resources scarce, and order scarcer, force tended to be the only law. Early attempts at rebuilding were made for hundreds of years, but, out of system infrastructure was very, VERY difficult to build and maintain because of the lack of FTL.

  Most attempts have been unsuccessful, but there are a few exceptions, One such successor of the Crepitum is a faction known as the Danzyg Trade Union.

  As the name suggests, it's a large and powerful trade union that holds powers in most of the modern galaxy. It consists of a few organizations, namely, the Magimarches.

  * The Magimarches are a feudal state, which lends itself nicely to a world that is largely dictated by sub-light travel. It had come to be after The Crown used a series of connections and bribery to coerce the staff to swear fealty, where they now support and operate an ancient interstellar merchant-marine. In recent times, the Crown was allowed to spread freely, but it came into friction with the Danzyg Trade Union -- joining after being offered an executive position.

</Document>
