<Document>
  ## Maioris Ecclesiae

  Quick reference for Ecclesia players;
  - Follow the eight commandments, in their spirit and not just in body.
  - Hold Mass, especially on Sunday. During mass; pray, worship, listen to the bible (Homily), and consecrate. Hand out Eucharists (bread and wine). Do baptism.
  - Absolve as much suffering as possible, so you may become a Saint.

  ## The Eight Commandments
  - 1. I am the Lord thy God. Thou shall not have strange gods before Me.
  - 2. Thou shall not take the name of the Lord thy God in vain.
  - 3. Remember to keep holy the Lord's day.
  - 4. Thou shall not kill.
  - 5. Thou shall not commit adultery.
  - 6. Thou shall not steal.
  - 7. Thou shall not bear false witness against thy neighbor.
  - 8. Thou shall not covet thy neighbor's goods.

  "Maioris Ecclesiae (or, Mairoris for short, haha..) is a hot topic in the DTU. Despite having only been formed ten years ago, they're sweeping across the Union with promises of a better future -- for everyone.

  The cult started on a well to-do waystation named Alessandria, with a classic story about changes in the trade-route drafting meaning that the colonists wouldn't be receiving new food shipments for another month at that point. See: this is important because they had been on intense rationing for weeks, and some of them were dropping. Now, like usual, they turned on eachother.. but a local named Caorle stepped forth with a solution. See, they had been plagued with a Xeno infestation just a few weeks back.. and apparently the man had figured out a way to eat them -- through a form of consecration.

  The trick is that `*how*` was a closely held secret, only available to "true believers" of his practically unheard of faith.. of which there were a few in the crowd. Despite this, he had shared his resources freely. As of October this year, there's estimated to be as many as five thousand members! This puts them high--"

  A cult-like organization holding pre-Crepitum beliefs and knowledge. They believe in a singular God, who gave unto them eight commandments superseding all other laws. They believe that God is himself, his son Jesus, and the spirit of him, his orders, and his people in a Holy Trinity. They believe that God offered a person his son, and they accepted, freeing them from sin. They believe in an afterlife, and that there are two kinds; heaven, and hell. Heaven is the kingdom of God where good actions in the previous life are rewarded for eternity, Hell being the place where bad behavior is punished.

  The Ecclesia believe that in order to enter heaven one must be free from sin. Contradicting this, they also believe that all people have sinned (as per the words of their savior, Jesus Christ). So, how does one enter heaven? Repentance! By repenting, they can offer up their suffering in a transitory afterlife called Purgatory, where they are freed from the physical effects of their sins and allowed into heaven.

  There are quite a few ways of repenting, but they take on three main forms. Fasting (acts of self discipline), Prayer, and Almsgiving. In many cases, the most common form of repentance is private confession of sin to a priest that is closely followed by absolution. That being said: being forgiven by Jesus does not automatically grant you entry into heaven. You still need to repent.

</Document>
