<Document>
  ## Primer
  It's the year 1315 (Post Crepitum). Much of the natural world has been ruined by war and greed, leaving the living vastly outnumbered by the dead. Yet, we still persist. One such successor of the Corporate War is a faction known as the Magimarches, led by an enigmatic figure known as The Crown.

  The Magimarches are a feudal state, which lends itself nicely to a world that is largely dictated by sub-light travel. It had come to be after The Crown used a series of connections and bribery to coerce the staff to swear fealty, where they now support and operate an ancient interstellar merchant-marine. In recent times, the Crown was allowed to spread freely, but it came into friction with the Danzyg Trade Union -- joining after being offered an executive position.

  As of six months ago, the most war torn section of space known as the Null Sector was made accessible for the first time since the Crepitum. News quickly spread, and a sort of modern gold rush started as tens of thousands flock to the riches hidden by the entropic field for centuries.

  But, not all is well. The Danzyg Trade Union is a powerful, roiling force -- and it's pressing the Crown with higher and higher tariffs, not to mention the bandits and anomalies that plague the Magimarches.

  Out of a desire to adapt, the Crown drafted an expedition to the Null Sector. Initially, none of the Shipbarons volunteered.. but one such member of Magimarches' Merchant Marine -- the DTU "Arion" -- did.

  It's a historied vessel with a record of service going all the way back to the Corporate Wars, and one of the first to pledge fealty to The Crown. Once a combat transport, it finds itself retrofitted for cargo hauling. It was designed with light armor and an overclocked shield array, which it still employs to this day. At one point, it was *just* for cargo hauling, but as of the drafting, it was refitted even further with a science department and medical bay at an attempt to cover the facilities it may lack.

  [bold]You play as a crew member of the DTU "Arion", be it as a lowborn fuel jockey, or perhaps as a noble Shipbaron. You are to survive as best as you can, and ideally even thrive.[/bold]
</Document>
